Guide to the Connecticut Public Health Association Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Connecticut Public Health Association records
1916-1993
1946-1993
MS 1251
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
14.75
(16 boxes)
The records document the history of the Connecticut Public Health Association (1974) and its predecessors. Most materials date from 1946-1993 and consist of correspondence, minutes, bylaws, constitutions, newsletters, officers' reports, and memoranda relating to the business of the organizations. These papers form part of the Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection.
Connecticut Public Health Association
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Connecticut Public Health Association, 1981 and 1995.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The Connecticut Public Health Association (C.P.H.A.) is a private organization for individuals with professional or personal interest in public health and for state-wide organizations in health-related fields. It was founded in 1974 through a merger of the Connecticut Public Health Association and the Connecticut Health League (C.H.L.). The new organization was originally named the Connecticut Health Association, Inc., but reverted to the name of the larger of the two parent organizations in 1978. The original C.P.H.A. was founded in 1916 to protect and promote public health and safety in Connecticut. The C.H.L. developed out of a C.P.H.A. committee appointed to explore the need for a council to coordinate state health agencies. The C.H.L. was formed in 1951.
Scope and Contents
The records document the history of the Connecticut Public Health Association (1974) and its predecessors. Most materials date from 1946-1993 and consist of correspondence, minutes, bylaws, constitutions, newsletters, officers' reports, and memoranda relating to the business of the organizations. These papers form part of the Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by organization name.
Alcoholism; Public health; Water-supply -- Connecticut -- New Haven; New Haven (Conn.); Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection; Connecticut Health League; Connecticut Public Health Association
- Inventory
  - Connecticut Public Health Association (1916-1974)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association (CPHA) constitution and bylaws, minutes of business and board of directors' meetings, newsletters, officer and committee reports, American Public Health Association (APHA) delegate reports, correspondence, 1954-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1-20)
      Scope and Contents
      Materials have been removed from binders.
    - APHA memoranda and attachments, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Constitution, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings, 1936 December 16 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Bylaws, 1937-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Programs, 1946-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1947-1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - APHA and CPHA correspondence, 1948-1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Annual meetings and board of directors' meetings minutes, 1948-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Committees, 1948, 1952-1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Organization of Connecticut Health League and CPHA representative, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Constitution, 1950-1952 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Minutes of Board of Directors' and annual meetings, 1950-1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1916, 1950-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Annual meeting, Uncas-on-Thames, 1953 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Health Officers meeting, 1953 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Organization membership, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Annual meeting, Norwich, 1953 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Pending correspondence, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - APHA, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Board of directors, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - CPHA News, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Membership list and meeting notes, 1953-1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - MacCalmont, 1953-1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Membership, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Annual meeting, Meriden, 1954 May 13 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Deputy Commissioner, State Department of Health, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - APHA membership secretary, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Publicity Committee, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Dorothy Kirk, 1954-1961 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Eloise Eckler, Treasurer, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Legislation, correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, minutes, and print material of the Public Health Careers Committee, 1956-1962 (Box 3)
    - Documents and audiotape dealing with fluoridation of the public water supply in New Haven, 1955-1964 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, minutes, and committee files of the CPHA, 1955-1967 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' and annual meeting minutes, correspondence, and committee files, 1959-1967 (Box 4)
    - Board of directors' minutes and correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 5)
    - Research material collected by the CPHA historian for the association's 50th anniversary, Circa 1966 (Box 6)
    - American Public Health Association Governing Council meeting material, Circa 1954-1965 (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, board of directors' minutes, and committee files, 1916-1972 (Box 6)
    - Public Issues Committee material, publicity, newsletters, programs, and clippings, 1949-1974 (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Health League
    - Secretary's books and other material, 1950-1960 (Box 8)
      Documents the formation of the League, Conference on Aging, Health Careers project, and relations with the National Health Council. Secretary's books include correspondence, minutes, and reports.
    - Secretary's books, 1958-1961 (Box 9)
      Includes Connecticut School Health Council, Alcoholism Study, and other projects.
    - Secretary's books, 1962-1974 (Box 10)
      Includes information on merger with CPHA.
  - Connecticut Public Health Association (post 1974)
    - Material documenting formation of Connecticut Health Association and early operations, 1974-1978 (Box 10)
      CHA name changed to CPHA in 1978.
- Additional materials, 1950-1957; Accession 1982-M-002
  - Connecticut Health League
    - Organization, 1950-1951 (Box 1)
    - Administrators Conference, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Delegates and dues, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Finance committee, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Nominating committee, 1951 Feb, December (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 1)
    - Membership committee, 1951-1953 (Box 1)
    - Meetings and agendas, 1951-1954 (Box 1)
    - Local Health Councils, 1951-1956 (Box 1)
    - Administrators Conference, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Delegates and dues, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Yale workshop, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Health Education committee, 1952-1953 (Box 1)
    - Project Review committee, 1952-1953 (Box 1)
    - Committees, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Conference on Aging, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Dues, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Delegates, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Health Education committee, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Conference on Aging, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Fluoridation, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Legislation committee, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Nominating committee, 1953 Jan, December (Box 1)
    - Program committee, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Publicity committee, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Second annual meeting, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Annual meeting, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Delegates, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Dues, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Third annual meeting, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Coordination Voluntary Health Agency, 1954-1957 (Box 2)
    - Annual and semi-annual meetings, 1955 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors, 1955 (Box 2)
    - Program committee, 1955 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Committees: general, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Minutes, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Legislative committee, 1956 (Box 2)
    - Dues, 1957 (Box 2)
    - Application forms, Undated (Box 2)
- Additional material, 1974-1993; Accession 1995-M-128
  The bulk of the material dates from 1978-1993 and consists of minutes of meetings, committee reports, newsletters, and financial statements of the Connecticut Public Health Association (CPHA). There is also some material of the CPHA from 1950-1974, and a small quantity of material which dates from the time of the merger of the CPHA and the Connecticut Health League and from the first years of the association when it was known as the Connecticut Health Association.
  Arrangement
  The files are arranged by year and then by type of material, as received from the Connecticut Public Health Association.
  - Connecticut Health League
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Financial report, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Public Health Association and Connecticut Health League
    - Joint meetings, 1973 (Box 1)
      - Merger, 1974 (Box 1)
      - Program, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Health Association
    - Bylaws, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Financial report and organization members, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Certificate of incorporation, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Financial statement, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Committee reports, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1975 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Resolutions, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Forum on Planning and Resources Development Act, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Program on health legislation, 1976 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Communications workshop, 1976 (Box 1)
    - New England Public Health Association (NEPHA), 1976 (Box 1)
    - Newsletter, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Officers, board of directors and membership, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Financial report, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meeting, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Awards and education committee reports, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Program, public issues and nominating committee reports, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Resolution, including name change to CPHA, 1977 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Public Health Association
    - Officers and board of directors, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Newsletter, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Officers, 1937-1954 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Newsletter, 1954 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1955-1956 (Box 1)
    - Officers, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Newsletter, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Officers, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Articles of incorporation, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Revised bylaws, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Newsletter, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Officers, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Draft bylaws, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1964 (Box 1)
    - NEPHA, 1964 (Box 1)
    - IRS tax exempt request, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1965 (Box 1)
    - IRS tax exemption, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Directors of health, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Fiftieth anniversary meeting, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Newsletter, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Income tax return/financial statement, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Officers, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Income tax return and financial statement, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Income tax return, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Income tax return and financial statement, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Resolution on smoking, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Minutes of annual meeting, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Financial statement, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
    - Annual meeting, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Federal Immunization Indemnity Corporation, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1978 (Box 1)
    - New Haven Foundation and financial report, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Committee reports, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Resolutions, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Legislative advocacy, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Press releases, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Budget and financial report, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Committee reports, 1979 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1979 (Box 1)
    - NEPHA, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Financial report, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Committee reports, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Resolutions, 1980 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1980 (Box 1)
    - NEPHA, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Budget and financial statement, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Committee reports, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Continuing education program, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Health Care Expo, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Futures Task Force, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Awards, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Resolutions, 1981 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1981 (Box 1)
    - NEPHA, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Membership, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Budget and financial report, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Committee reports, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Continuing education programs, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Health Care Expo, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Futures Task Force, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Awards, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Semi-annual and annual meeting, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Resolutions, 1982 (Box 1)
    - APHA, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Newsletters, 1982 (Box 1)
    - NEPHA, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Bylaws, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Budget and financial statement, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Continuing education program, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Futures Task Force, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1983 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Public Health Research and Education Trust (CREF), 1983 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 2)
    - NEPHA, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Budget and financial report, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Continuing education program, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Semi-annual and annual meeting, 1984 (Box 2)
    - CREF, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Advisory School Health Council (CASHC), 1984 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters, 1984 (Box 2)
    - NEPHA, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Budget and financial report, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Continuing education program, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Semi-annual and annual meetings, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Position paper, 1985 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 2)
    - NEPHA, 1985 (Box 2)
    - CASHC, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Budget and financial statement, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Continuing education program, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Semi-annual and annual meeting, 1986 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Policy statements, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters and news briefs, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Financial report, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Semi-annual and annual meeting, 1987 (Box 2)
    - AIDS benefit, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Proposed resolution, policy statement and position paper, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Continuing education program, 1987 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1987 (Box 2)
    - CREF, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters and news briefs, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Financial reports, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Children in crisis grant announcement, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Children in crisis benefit, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Annual meeting, 1988 (Box 2)
    - CREF, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Grant application for full-time public health service, 1988 (Box 2)
    - CASHC, 1988 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters/news briefs, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Membership, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Budget and financial report, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Committee reports, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Board of directors' retreat, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Annual meeting, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Points of Light presentation, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Resolutions, 1989 (Box 2)
    - APHA, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Testimony before Connecticut legislature, 1989 (Box 2)
    - CREF course on marketing, 1989 (Box 2)
    - CASHC, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Newsletters and news briefs, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Membership, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Financial report, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Committee reports, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' retreat, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Annual retreat, 1990 (Box 3)
    - CREF grant for minorities, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Continuing education program, 1990 (Box 3)
    - APHA, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Grant for the future of public health, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Healthy Connecticut Coalition, 1990 (Box 3)
    - NEPHA, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Membership, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Financial report, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Committee reports, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Awards reception, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Annual meeting, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Radon risk project, 1991 (Box 3)
    - APHA, 1991 (Box 3)
    - CREF, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Healthy Connecticut Coalition, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Membership, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Budget and financial report, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Committee reports, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' retreat, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Annual meeting, 1992 (Box 3)
    - CREF, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Proposed contracts, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Resolutions, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Policy statements, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Legislative breakfast, 1992 (Box 3)
    - APHA, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Healthy Connecticut Coalition, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Radon risk project, 1992 (Box 3)
    - NEPHA, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous information I & II, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Officers and board of directors, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' meeting minutes, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Budget and financial report, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Committee reports, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Semi-annual meeting, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Annual meeting, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Board of directors' retreat, 1993 (Box 4)
    - APHA, 1993 (Box 4)
      - Year 2000 objectives, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Radon risk project, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Healthy Connecticut Coalition, 1993 (Box 4)
    - CASHC, 1993 (Box 4)
    - NEPHA, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous information, 1993 (Box 4)